

Boise, Idaho



208-954-1271



hannah.milam16@gmail.com



github.com/hannahmilam



linkedin.com/in/hannah-milam

Hannah Milam

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Dedicated software developer with prior strong leadership skills from running a dental practice for several years. Passionate about software development, building beautiful user friendly applications with a love for problem solving. Seeking an opportunity with your company to provide my skills with Object-Oriented Design, Vue, C#, .Net, and JavaScript.

SKILL

- HTML/CSS
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- Vue.js
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- Mongoose
- C#/.Net
- Agile/Scrum
- MySQL

APPLICATIONS

PRESSPLAY

- Collaborative application for musicians
- Fullstack application utilizing Javascript, vue, mongoDb, and firebase.

BUGLOG

- Fullstack application utilizing Vue,
 MongoDb, Javascript, and Bootstrap.
- Organizes and logs bugs that are currently open/closed

EDUCATION

FullStack Software Development

BoiseCodeworks | Aug 2021 - Nov 2021

EXPERIENCE

Software Development Student

CodeWorks | Aug 2021 - Nov 2021

- Learned full-stack development including HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Vue, Node, Mongo.db, C#, DotNet, and MySQL
- Implemented the scrum process during several group applications
- Gained organization skills, and how to have precise clean code that is structured and up to standards.

Dental Office Mangager

Eagle Dental Care | Aug 2017 - Aug 2021

- Promoted to Dental Office Manager from Dental Assistant in 2019 due to my work ethic, leadership skills, and strong knowledge of dental insurance, claims, and running an office.
- Processed over 50 insurance payments per day, as well as submitted dental claims on behalf of the patient.
- Implemented monthly, quarterly, yearly spreadsheets to keep data for the dental office's stats which helped track our data.
- Increased monthly profit by 55% by getting carecredit established at our practice, implementing coverage tables for every patient to maximize their benefits.
- Verified over 40 patients insurance benefits per day and added them into their coverage tables.